https://www.atlatt.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Innovative Technology for the Sewn Products Industry Worldwide
Search for:
Replacement Parts
Search for:
Home / About Us / Privacy Policy
Atlanta Attachment Company is very concerned about the protection of online privacy for all of our Web site visitors. Although we track the total number of visitors to each of our sites in an aggregate form to allow us to update and improve our sites, personally identifiable information is not extracted in this process. Any cookie technology (where our servers deposit special codes on a visitor’s computer) will only be used to track non-personal information such as type of browser, operating system, and domain names to improve our visitors’ online experience.
Atlanta Attachment Company only collects personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, email addresses and the like, when voluntarily submitted by a visitor in an e-mail request for sales, service, or in response to one of our online surveys. Atlanta Attachment Company does not release any information (i.e. names, addresses or phone numbers) gathered on our Web sites to any third parties outside of our strategic product and service partners; all information gathered online will be used by Atlanta Attachment Company to improve our product and service offerings. Information submitted such as news, industry articles, success stories, press releases and industry/personal recognition may be posted on the Web site.
In some instances, when a visitor has indicated that he/she would like to receive communications from us, we will contact visitors. Our modes of contact may include e-mail, newsletters, site visits, printed newsletters and brochures and other electronic and non electronic mail.
Atlanta Attachment Company reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence of a new privacy policy. This will be done by placing the amendments or changes to the policy on this page with the date that the changes are being implemented.
For any questions concerning this privacy policy please contact Atlanta Attachment Company at:
E-mail
Atlanta Attachment Company
Phone
+1-770-963-7369
Mail
Atlanta Attachment Company
ATTN: Web Site Administrator
362 Industrial Park Drive
Directions
Atlanta Precision (APMF)
HSM
Loan Calculator
Catalogs
Apparel Catalog
Apparel Catalog – Spanish
Automotive Catalog
Folders Catalog
Furniture Catalog
A tremendous asset…
Johnson City Bedding Co.
Company Video
Take a few minutes to watch our company video.
362 Industrial Park Drive, Lawrenceville, GA 30046, USA | +1 (770) 963-7369 | FAX +1 (770) 963-7641 | sales@atlatt.com
© 2020 Atlanta Attachment Co.
Home
Mattress
Automotive
Apparel
Furniture
Folders & Attachments
Parts
Support
Website Design & Digital Marketing Agency - Jump 2 IT Media Ltd.
Contact Us
Message*First Name*Last Name*Company*City*State*State*AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces PacificCountryAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d'IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMauritaniaMauritiusMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSudan, SouthSurinameSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.YemenZambiaZimbabweEmail*
Phone*EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
